<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Claire Spencer&#39;s Github Site</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Claire Spencer&#39;s Github Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Of the seven times the Huskers&#39; mens basketball team qualified for the NCAA tournament, what season prior were they the strongest?</title>
      <link>/2022/04/26/of-the-seven-times-the-huskers-mens-basketball-team-qualified-for-the-ncaa-tournament-what-season-prior-were-they-the-strongest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/26/of-the-seven-times-the-huskers-mens-basketball-team-qualified-for-the-ncaa-tournament-what-season-prior-were-they-the-strongest/</guid>
      <description>The Huskers’ mens basketball team has successfully made it to the first and second round of the NCAA tournament a total of seven times. Over the course of these seasons, Moe Iba, Tim Miles, and Danny Nee all had a chance to experience the tournament. But, what season prior to March Madness were the Huskers’ the most successful to get them qualified?
First, let’s look at the total wins and losses for each season, with the most games played at the top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Claire Spencer</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Claire Spencer, and I am a sophomore at the University of Nebraska-Lincoln. I am majoring in broadcasting and sports media &amp;amp; communications with a minor in film studies. I hope to work with professional sports teams doing video content production and media creating in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What NCAA Big Ten team was the most accurate with their shooting in the 2021-22 season?</title>
      <link>/2022/04/06/what-ncaa-big-ten-team-was-the-most-accurate-with-their-shooting-in-the-2021-22-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/06/what-ncaa-big-ten-team-was-the-most-accurate-with-their-shooting-in-the-2021-22-season/</guid>
      <description>We love to cheer on our NCAA Big Ten teams in a crowd full of screaming fans, right? Because everyone knows the Big Ten has the greatest fans in college sports. But it isn’t so enjoyable hearing those loud ’BOO’s when your team misses the winning shot, right? When we take into account all of these shots, sink or miss, what team comes out on top this season?
First, lets look at the field goal percentages for each Big Ten team this season.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
